#### Contact

9588908842 (Mobile) eshaan\_2345@yahoo.co.in

www.linkedin.com/in/eshaanchauhan-1a9989152 (LinkedIn) eshaan1.blogspot.com (Personal)

## Top Skills

Digital Marketing
Microsoft Office
Facebook Marketing

### Languages

Korean (Limited Working)
Hindi (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

### Certifications

data science certificate
LinkedIn Learning For professionals
udemy indie game development
course

Responsive Web Design Python for Data Science

# Eshaan Chauhan

Chatbot Developer | Digital Marketing | Data Analyst | Web Developer | Front -end, Back-end Developer | Consultant Mumbai

## Summary

I am a developer and I have a command over python,full stack web developer, digital marketing etc. The things that I do the most is marketing like search email marketing, digital and media marketing, SEO, design(web design, and data analytics are my area of expertise. I am studying computer science in the city of Jaipur and like to explore my options and also like to work on project so that I can improve my skills.

## Experience

Above the Standard Global Partner August 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month) Jaipur Area, India

Our global network includes more than a thousand certified suppliers, tenured experts,

strategic partners, and representation in many nations. We have worked in Non-profit,

Government, Private, Public, Commercial, Universities, and much more.

What are Some Above the Standard Success Stories?

We have many client success stories for small to large organizations, private and public held, in

non- profit, and Government, within Universities, and teams from many nations!

Check us out a http://www.abovethestandard.net/

- 30+ Years
- 28%+ Average Profit Increase
- 98% Success for Engaged Clients
- Tens of Billions Saved (Increased Profits)

- Introduce Prospect by Email
- Global Organization

Google Local Guides
Google local guide
June 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months)
Jaipur Area, India

I am a level 6 local guide who reviews places around the world.

InCampus Ltd Human Resources Intern May 2020 - July 2020 (3 months) India

I was a human resource intern for incampus and was a part of the recruitment team and in my two months internship I interviewed about 90 people in that period of time. it was a great experience while working in incampus.

Edvizo
Social Media Marketing Intern
April 2020 - July 2020 (4 months)
Mumbai Metropolitan Region
social media marketing intern

BeingDatum
Data Science Intern
March 2020 - June 2020 (4 months)
Mumbai, Maharashtra

I worked on building new models and application related to data science ,Made a chatbot for the company website where any student who needs document related to machine learning ,data science can access it, how to connect, retrieve data from database ,use of python and rasa framework for chatbot creation , and learned how to integrate rasa chatbot with custom chat widget. Along with that, I have written some blogs on Rasa and slack integration with rasa chatbot which is published on the Being Datum portal.

Future IM/Pact
Investment Management
April 2020 - May 2020 (2 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra

It was a virtual internship were is learned and done task on-

Overview of industry key players
Fixed income investing
Make an investment recommendation
for Apple stock (Bonus module)
A day in the life of an Analyst
Roles and career pathways in
Investment Management

Self employed 3 years 10 months

I do freelancing in different website. May 2017 - March 2020 (2 years 11 months) Jaipur Area, India

I do content writing ,video editing ,digital marketing. June 2016 - September 2017 (1 year 4 months) Jaipur Area, India

### ALHANSAT TECHNOLOGIES

Python Developer January 2020 - February 2020 (2 months) Work from home

To visually represent and plot interactive graphs of Engineering Mathematics topics using Python.

The topic which was assigned to me was Linear Differential Equations with Constant Coefficients and Variable Coefficients of Higher Order. It was a great experience and i was able to apply my knowledge while doing the internship.

Internshala
Internshala Student Partner 15
August 2019 - November 2019 (4 months)
Jaipur Area, India

It was a great experience for me as I was able to learn a lot from this student partner internship. Thank you internshala for this opportunity.

Doalongme
Full Stack Web Developer
September 2019 - October 2019 (2 months)
Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh, india

I was a full-stack web developer for this company where I build website for clients through the company. The company as a whole is very nice and I was able to learn a lot from them.

Wrytin Content Writer July 2019 - August 2019 (2 months) Jaipur Area, India

It was a internship in which I had to write about 32 article in a month and the company that I worked at was very nice and I was able to learn many things while doing this internship

Unschool Sales And Marketing Intern May 2019 - June 2019 (2 months)

I was a sales and marketing intern at unschool

# Education

Swami Keshvanand Institute of Technology
Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

Navy Children School high school degree, science · (2015 - 2017)